Help me! Somebody help!
Somebody, help!
Help me!
Gin!
Read them and weep.
Finally!
- All right.
- You ready?
- War.
- War?
We're not playing war.
War's not even a game.
- We are too playing war. Come on.
- It's total chance, Stace.
Winner picks the game, Jeff.
That's your rules.
Thank you, Amy.
Okay. War.
Okay. Who wants
a little Mexican hair of the dog?
Senorita Margarita.
- I'll have some.
- You'll definitely have some.
- Come on, Jeff.
- No, keep that away from me.
Well, that's not what you were saying
last night.
Seriously, Mr. Nude Lifeguard.
What was up with that?
I don't know
what you guys are talking about.
One, two, three, four, I declare war.
You're burning up, honey.
- What do you mean?
- You're all red.
- No, I'm flushed. I'm just hot.
- You're not flushed.
- I finally won.
- Good.
- I knew you would.
- You did?
- Okay.
- I did. Of course I did.
- Shit!
- What?
I lost my earring.
Why don't you look
under the towel there?
Is it under your chair?
- Look under your towel.
- It's not.
- Under your towel.
- Why would it be under our towel?
- I don't know, I think I was...
- Did you come lay under here?
- We're gonna find it, honey.
- It's my favorite earring.
It's probably in the pool.
I found it. It's yours, I think.
Yeah?
- Thank you so much!
- Thank you.
It's not a problem.
Hey, do you want a drink?
Yeah, sure. Thank you.
It's got ice in it.
It's okay.
It's blended.
- That means it has ice, Eric.
- Thank you.
- Where are you from?
- Munich, originally.
Stace, it's just ice.
No, it's not. The water system here
is contaminated with human feces.
Okay? So your drinks are, like, blended
with hepatitis B. Yes. Hepatitis B.
How do you know each other?
They're best friends,
and we're their boyfriends.
Cool.
How about you?
Are you here by yourself?
No, with my brother,
but he left with some girl, yeah.
Left here? Mexico or...
Oh, no, no. She's an archeologist.
He went with her to a dig site.
- And what are they digging?
- Like an excavation?
Yeah, it's ruins, I think. A Mayan temple.
Kind of like the ones
- that nobody here wanted to go to...
- Yes, Jeff.
...the entire time that we've been here.
Apparently, it's not even
in the guidebooks.
VIP only.
Yeah. See, Jeff,
that's something I would do.
- Oh, yeah?
- Sounds like fun.
Well, if you're interested,
I'm going there tomorrow.
Heinrich was supposed to be
back by now,
but he must be having a good time.
So what do you guys think?
Ancient Mayan temple
off the beaten path?
I don't know,
a little culture before we leave?
I wanna go.
- You will?
- Yeah.
Since I just kicked Jeff's ass in cards,
I got nothing left to do here.
Wow!
Wow.
- Wow.
- Say something.
Eric?
Well, yeah, I mean, as long as I'm back
for make-your-own-taco night, I'm in.
Amy?
Do we have to wake up early?
Hey, malaka...
You come to beach tonight? To party?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay.
They are supposed to be
coming with me tomorrow,
but maybe it's a big mistake.
They're all fucking crazy in the head.
So, there was this hotel heiress
who dyed her hair blonde.
But the carpet didn't match the drapes.
So she stripped it away.
What is it? What's the joke?
What's so funny? I'm not...
You don't want to know, Mathias.
But the hardwood floor underneath it
was all scuffed up and dirty!
So she buffed it.
But then it was too slippery.
Who's gonna dance with me?
Come on. Come on.
I'm just not feeling this one.
Jeff, buddy, we got two days left.
I wanna see some moves.
It's just like playing the trombone.
Jeff used to play the trombone
in high school.
- Jeffrey on the trombone, nice!
- He won a prize.
Thank you for sharing that
with everybody.
Now he's gonna be a doctor.
And he's gonna win a prize for that.
Mathias!
Hey, the Greeks!
Hey, what's up? How are you?
Amy! Amy! No, no! No!
- Amy! No, no, no, no!
- Amy!
I'll take some. I'll take some.
I have her.
Amy, it's time to go to bed. Let's go.
No, I don't want to.
Come on.
All right, I'm calling it a night, guys.
- Good night. Give me a kiss.
- Come here.
- Give me a kiss.
- Stay.
- See you, buddy!
- Make sure she gets home.
- Night, Jeff!
- Okay?
- I'll see you guys tomorrow morning.
- All right.
- Yeah.
- Be good, man.
- My boyfriend, the rock star!
- See you, Ame.
- Matteo!
- Mathias.
Mathias.
Show me a German dance. Come on.
You want a German dance?
Like a waltz?
- Come on!
- Yeah...
Drag you?
Nobody wants to dance!
- You want me to dance? I can't dance.
- It's so beautiful!
So, how much you wanna bet
she kisses him?
She's freaking out 'cause Jeff's med
school is like 2,000 miles away, okay?
- You do a twirl.
- Okay, how much?
- She's not gonna kiss him.
- That's nice.
- Yeah, it's good, yeah?
- Yeah, how do you do that?
All right, you know what?
Oral sex. Winner receives.
Oral sex. Okay.
- All right, more of the hips.
- Use the hips. Like this.
Jeff's a nice guy, yeah.
Come here. Come here.
I wanna tell you a secret.
Amy!
- Yes!
- Amy!
- What are you doing?
I will dance with you, okay?
Crazy Greeks.
No. The place that they went, here.
It's only on this old map.
It's gone from the guidebook.
What are you doing?
He's making a copy of the map from
the girl Heinrich met, for his friends.
Yes, your friends look like
they could use a map.
All right. Give me a couple of minutes?
- Rally the troops?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Half an hour in the lobby?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- All right.
Do you know
what they do to people down here
who don't honor their bets?
Bus leaves in like 15 minutes.
They smash their hands.
No, they do. They take broomsticks,
and they just like, whack,
smash their hands.
I mean, it's a true story.
It's kind of brutal, but it happens.
What are you gonna do?
- Get up! Get up!
- Come on!
Come on! Jeff's gonna be pissed
if we miss it.
The terrible wrath of Jeff,
followed, I'm sure, by the even more
frightening whining of Amy.
She's not that bad.
No, but I bet she's feeling pretty
awkward right about now, don't you?
Don't say anything.
I mean it. Not a word.
- Come here.
- Come on!
Look, be a shame
to smash these pretty little hands.
Will you please get in the shower?
Come here for a second. Come here.
Come here.
You know,
you're in Mexico now, muchacha.
Muchacha?
And you can't just lose a bet like that
and expect to walk away free.
How much do I owe you again?
I'll be quick. So quick.
Okay.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
You don't sound fine, honey.
Hey, that's really helpful, thanks.
Here you go. Come on.
Let's get going.
- Maybe I shouldn't go.
- What?
You're gonna be back tonight.
I'll just, like, sleep until then.
You wanna spend
our last day sleeping?
I'll just hang out, like read or something.
Amy. Come on.
People come from all over the world
just to see these ruins.
And this one isn't even on the map.
I'm not taking you
to some tourist trap, honey.
Don't you wanna have some experience
or something to shoot,
other than just the beach, the pool,
the beach, the pool?
Well, you're already dressed.
You might as well just go without me.
Hey.
But I don't wanna go without you.
- Okay, let's go.
- Yeah?
- Okay.
Ready?
What are you so happy about?
Watch out for that.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
- Amy, there's a puppy!
- Heinrich?
Hello?
- What?
- I don't know.
So, now what?
We take taxi.
- How far?
- 18 kilometers.
Hey, how many miles is that?
It's about 11. Maybe a little bit more.
Then there's a path,
which we hike for 4 kilometers.
2.5 miles.
Okay, no one said anything
about a hike.
Amy!
- Stacy!
- Come here!
Well, I don't see any cabs.
That's a bit of a problem.
What?
- Yeah.
- I don't know what you're saying.
There we go.
Why?
No, it's good. Is there a mirror?
How much, you drive us here?
No, no. This place, no good.
I'll drive you to pyramid.
Muy grande. Everybody go.
I take you. I take you.
Yes.
- Hey! Amy, Stace!
- Bye, puppy!
I wanna stay with the puppy.
- Let's go!
- You guys ready?
- We got new hats.
- Very nice.
- This is the taxi?
- Yeah, this is it. Come on. Let's go.
My pants are gonna get dirty.
Hey, Jeff. Can you give me some water?
Take a picture.
- Is this it?
- Yeah, this must be.
How you feeling?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Oh, my God, I'm so glad that's over.
You okay?
- My jeans are all dirty.
- Do you have a telefono?
Thanks.
Bye, puppy!
Wait, how are we gonna get back?
We're gonna call him when we get out.
With what?
We're not gonna get a signal out here.
My phone should work.
It's a world phone.
Hello? Can you hear me now?
It's not funny, Eric.
It's like a 20-mile hike
I'm gonna do in flip-flops.
Eleven.
It's a little funny.
Yeah, it's working.
- Problem solved.
- Can I have my sunglasses?
Is that your brother's Jeep?
Yeah, it is.
It's not funny.
It's a little funny.
We go. Coming?
Yeah, yeah. Come on, let's go. Ready?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
Want a piggyback ride?
- No.
- No?
So, there was this girl who got really,
really drunk one night.
But she sobered up really,
really quickly.
Who is this?
Just the stupid game
that they were playing last night.
But not before she stuck
her tongue down some guy's throat.
Eric.
How much further is it?
We cross a stream,
then there should be a path to the left.
If we seen a village,
then we've gone too far.
Wait, there's a village?
Yeah. A Mayan village.
Why did we leave the hotel again?
Whoa!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Just almost fell.
- Fucking stinks.
- Whoa.
You stink.
- How much further past the stream is it?
- You're funny.
Right after, it says.
Yeah, well, I don't see any path.
Can I have some... Thanks.
My legs are sore.
Look!
Don't scare them.
I'm not gonna scare them. Hello!
They look sad.
Hello?
- You guys wanna go talk to them?
- Yeah.
Maybe they can guide us.
I don't think they speak Spanish.
Look.
Where's he going?
It's here. This must be it.
That's the path?
Why was it covered?
I don't think that's the right path.
- It's on the map?
- Yeah.
It's on the map.
Jeff, do you see how old
that map looks?
And it was covered.
Why would it be covered?
Maybe the archeologists don't want
people to find their site, guys.
Great. They're gonna be thrilled
to see us then.
No, maybe they just found something
valuable, you know,
and they don't want people to rob it,
and just get the Mayans
to keep people away.
- How far away is it?
- It's not far.
- Just feels weird.
- Well, what do you wanna do?
Just turn around
and walk all the way back?
A hidden path
in the middle of the jungle.
So, do you think
those kids were Mayans?
I mean, aren't the Mayans extinct?
Didn't they die
of some fucked up disease?
That's great, Eric.
We could be walking through
an ancient graveyard right now.
Like a bone depository or something.
- I doubt it.
- Yeah, I doubt it.
Did you just mimic me?
No, no, I was agreeing with you.
He was totally mimicking you.
Was I? Was I really?
Wow.
Oh, wow.
- Finally!
- I think this is it.
See, honey?
Wow.
- It's beautiful.
- It is.
- Can I have my glasses?
- Yeah.
- Aren't you glad you came?
- Here.
Look, that's it.
Well, we made it.
Can I have a drink? Thank you.
Hey, Stace.
Mexico!
I know I'm a dork.
Mathias?
Is that a tent?
Where?
Up there in the corner.
Good job!
Heinrich!
Maybe he wants some money.
What, like a toll or something?
Amy. Stop.
What the fuck do they want?
Show a picture of your brother.
On the phone.
Wait.
- We're trying to find...
- You seen him?
- Ame, don't move!
- Stop!
- Amy! Amy!
- Okay.
Don't move. Just don't move.
- Give to them! Give to them fotografia!
- Jeff!
- Give to me camera.
- Ame, don't move!
Hey!
- What the hell was that?
- Dimitri.
Want the camera?
Easy. Easy, just...
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Stop!
- Amy! Amy!
- Oh, God!
Jeff!
Heinrich!
I need to stop.
- I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
- Stace. Stace. Look at me.
- I can't breathe.
- Stacy! Look at me!
Come on, we gotta go! Come on!
There's more coming!
Heinrich!
Oh, my God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, my God, Dimitri!
Oh, my God.
Why would they do that?
I can't breathe.
Eric, get your phone out.
There's no signal.
Really? Because if there was a signal
on the road you should be able to...
- No, I didn't get one.
- What do you mean?
- No, I mean, I never said...
- "Can you hear me now?"
- What the fuck was that, Eric?
- What the fuck? It was a joke!
Stop! Stop! Both of you, stop! Please!
Mathias had a signal.
Where's your phone?
The man. He took it.
Is it the dig?
Heinrich?
Maybe there's another way down.
My God...
Heinrich!
Oh, shit.
Oh, Jesus.
I'm sorry.
They keep coming.
They're setting up camps.
Why are they doing this?
Jesus Christ, they killed them both.
I mean what about the girl.
What happened to her?
- The one that Heinrich...
- Just stop it, Eric.
I mean, is she okay? Is she even here?
What happened?
Just stop it okay. Stop talking.
- Give the water, Amy.
- What happened?
It's the plant.
He's having some sort of
allergic reaction to it.
Why are they doing this?
Maybe they're preparing for something.
Like a sacrifice.
It has something to do with the ruins.
They won't come up here.
Now that we're here,
they won't let us leave.
So, what do we do,
just wait for someone to find us?
Who?
The Greeks.
Dimitri left them a copy of the map
before we left.
Yeah, and what if they decide
not to come, Jeff?
Then somebody else will.
We're supposed to check out
of the hotel tomorrow.
The hotel's gonna call the police.
When?
Tomorrow or the day after.
- Our flight is tomorrow, Jeff.
- I know, Amy.
But we know what happens if we leave.
Yeah, but what are we gonna eat?
Like, where do we sleep?
We should save this.
Hey, she's thirsty.
I know. We just don't have that much.
Well, why do you get to decide, Jeff?
Okay. Well, we can all decide.
But just keep in mind that each of us
needs a half a gallon of water
every day, just to survive.
And right now,
we don't even have a day's worth.
Maybe he's right.
What is that?
Hold on.
A cell phone?
- Heinrich's.
- Are you sure?
Yeah, it's his ringtone.
We had the same phone.
How can there be a signal?
There's not a signal up here.
It's definitely a phone.
Amy, in the orange tent,
there's a lantern hanging
and some matches on the ground.
Can you get them?
Eric?
- Eric.
- Yeah.
- Come figure this out. Drop that there.
- Okay.
Come on. Amy? All right, pull it now.
This thing needs to be off, right?
Come on.
Okay, okay. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- You got it?
- Yeah, that's it. Let's do this.
- Okay.
- Sure? You ready?
Yeah.
- Jeff? Jeff?
- Yeah?
The rope, I think...
- Whoa. Up, up, up!
- Wait, wait, wait!
- Pull it up! Up!
- Pull him up! Hurry!
- What?
- Hurry!
What is it? What?
Oh, shit.
Mathias!
- Mathias?
- Oh, my God.
- Jesus Christ.
- Oh, Jesus. Fuck. Fuck.
- Oh, my God.
Is he...
No, I can hear him.
One of you has to go.
Go? Go where?
Down. We're gonna check
the rest of the rope
and make sure it's secure.
And then one of you can...
Why do we have to go?
Why can't you or Eric?
'Cause you're not strong enough.
We need to work the crank.
I'll go.
- You will?
- Yeah.
Let me check.
Thank you.
Just help him into the sling,
and then we're gonna pull him out.
Once we get him out,
we're gonna drop the rope
and pull you back up, okay?
- Stace?
- Yeah?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Hey. You okay?
Yep.
Here you go.
- Stace, you gotta step off.
- We got you.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay.
You got it?
Stacy?
What?
It's the end of the rope!
I'm not at the bottom!
How much further is it?
Can you jump?
Can I what?
Please. Help me.
Okay.
Stace?
You okay?
I cut my knee!
Can you see Mathias?
Yeah, but it's dark!
We're gonna send the matches down.
Hurry!
Come on. Think.
What can we use?
What about the tents?
You know, we could take one down,
cut the nylon into strips.
I'm scared.
I can't move my legs.
You guys?
You guys, I think he broke his back!
He can't move his legs!
And it smells!
Like what?
Like shit!
We're gonna have to build a backboard.
No way. We can't move him.
Look, we are not
leaving him down there, okay?
How about the backpack frames
and the tent poles?
Are you listening to yourself?
Okay, this is insane.
We have to wait for help, okay?
Stacy, we have to build a backboard!
Okay.
Amy, there's tape in the tent.
Jeff, we cannot move someone
with a broken back, okay?
- Amy, we have no choice.
- You know that!
You have to go down
and help lift him on!
No.
- We have to tell them.
- Tell who?
We have to tell them.
Maybe they could call someone.
They can send for help.
Amy, they're not gonna send for help.
No, we have to try, Jeff.
Amy. Amy! Amy!
Amy!
Amy.
Amy! Ame.
Help us, please.
We need your help.
Someone's been hurt.
Amy, they can't understand you.
Say it in Spanish.
They don't speak Spanish, Ame.
- Just try!
- Ame.
Amy, they've already killed Dimitri.
I know you're scared.
I didn't want to come.
- Look at me. Amy. It's gonna be okay.
- I said I...
- I shouldn't be here.
- We're gonna get out of this.
Okay? Ame?
Please.
- They have to help us.
- Ame.
They have to. No, they have to!
Ame, Ame! Amy!
I don't want us to get shot, Ame. Please.
- Why won't you fucking help us?
- Ame!
Ame. Ame.
His mother was right there.
He touched the vine.
We all have.
Stacy?
Can you see it?
Is there anyone there?
I can't see it!
I wanna come back up!
- Okay.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
All right, let's go.
Stace, I'm coming down!
A few more feet!
That's all there is!
- We have to send it back up.
- No, no.
Amy, I can't stay down here any longer.
We can just lift him.
One of us at his shoulders,
the other person at his feet.
What if he twists?
It's only a couple of feet, Amy.
We can just lift him.
Can you still do it, Ame?
Okay!
I'm gonna try!
Mathias.
- Mathias, we're gonna lift you, okay?
- Okay.
We're gonna lift you up and out of here.
Okay.
- His hips.
- Are you sure?
If you lift him at the feet
he's gonna bend at the waist.
Yeah, but I lift him here from his hips,
it's gonna arch his back.
His knees.
Okay, quickly. On three, okay?
One, two, three!
Oh, my! Oh, my God!
Just get him on!
Pull him up!
Maybe we should carry him into the tent.
Squeeze my hand.
So he's not cold.
I don't think we should move him again.
Yeah, but we can't leave him out
in the open like this at night.
Let's see if we can find him
some aspirin or something, okay?
To keep his blood moving. Guys?
Look in the tents. Check the backpacks.
See what you guys can find.
Guys?
Look. Dimitri's plane ticket.
How does that help us?
He was supposed to leave
tomorrow morning.
On a 7:05 flight.
So when he doesn't show up tomorrow,
his friends are definitely gonna know
that something's wrong.
How will they know where we are?
They have the map.
Dimitri copied the map for them.
So they'll be here tomorrow.
We just have to make it through tonight.
That's it.
Maybe one of us should keep watch
while the other guys sleep.
Sleep?
It's working.
How is he?
We gotta keep his legs clean.
That's how it'll happen if it does.
If what does?
If he dies here.
Infection.
Jeff, he's not gonna die.
- Ame?
- Yeah?
I never should've said to lift him up,
should I?
I never should have said to lift him.
- Don't, Stace. Please.
- It's my fault.
Stace?
We're gonna get him
to the hospital tomorrow, okay?
He's gonna be okay.
Okay?
We just gotta rest.
Come on, Stace.
The Greeks will be here tomorrow.
Stace, come on.
Give me your hand.
Come closer.
- Eric!
- What?
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
- Eric!
- What?
- Get it off! Get it off! Get it off!
- Okay, okay.
Oh, my God. It's inside my leg.
Get it out! Get it out! Get it out!
- Get it out, get it out, get it out!
- Okay, okay.
Okay. Okay.
Oh, my God!
Okay, okay, okay.
Get it out.
What happened?
Help me.
Something's wrong.
Please. Something's wrong.
It's okay.
- Moving! I can feel it moving!
- Stop! No. I got it out!
- It's moving!
- Stace. What?
The vine, it was inside her.
- Show me my legs.
- Okay.
- Show me them!
Jeff!
- Jeff!
- Help me, please!
- Get it off me! Get it off!
- Jeff!
Help me!
Help me! Help me!
Take them off me!
Mathias! You just sit there and breathe.
Breathe, Mathias.
I'm gonna make a tourniquet right now.
I'm gonna cut off this bleeding, Mathias.
It's on our clothes.
It's... It's growing on us.
The phone.
I don't know how long these'll burn,
so you're gonna have to be quick.
I'd wait to light them
till you're both down there.
Link arms. One of you look to the right,
the other, your left.
You'll cover more ground that way.
Search a spot and then move on. Okay?
Okay!
Okay.
Be careful.
Amy, wait, wait.
Come on. We have to find it.
Just stay next to me.
Amy?
- That's where it's coming from.
- I can't.
- Come on.
- I don't wanna go in there. Amy.
We have to.
We have to find it.
It's okay, come on.
Okay.
Okay. Ame?
Hello?
Oh, my God.
The phone.
- It was just ringing.
- Let me see.
Yeah. It's cracked.
Amy.
Amy! Amy!
Oh, my God!
Go!
Run, Stace! Go!
Amy!
Jump on!
Pull us up! Pull it up!
Pull!
Go!
Come on!
- Are you okay, Ame?
- Get it off!
Did you find the phone, Amy?
- It's not a phone!
- Amy!
No, there is no fucking phone!
What happened?
Stace, what happened?
What do you mean,
the flower was making the ring?
It was vibrating
and it was ringing like a cell phone.
How? Amy, how does it do that?
I don't know, Eric. I don't know.
It was moving. It was alive.
It knows we're here.
We just have to go.
We have to go. We just...
We can't do that, Stace.
Jeff, you didn't see it. Okay?
I'm not staying here.
If we try to leave, they kill us.
Mathias can't move.
I can't just leave him here.
Okay, maybe we don't all have to go.
I mean, I could go. I can get help.
They have guns, Eric.
There are 50 of them, 60.
They killed that little kid, Amy.
Okay, so you guys make a distraction.
I can make it to the Jeep.
- I can do it.
- It's too dangerous, Eric.
- We have to wait.
- Wait for what, huh?
For the Greeks.
Jeff, the Greeks can't find
their own fucking hotel room.
- Eric.
- They're not gonna come out here
- and rescue us.
- We're being quarantined here.
We are being kept here to die!
This doesn't happen!
Four Americans on a vacation
don't just disappear!
Somebody,
the police, our parents,
the Greeks,
somebody,
somebody is going to find us.
We just have to be alive when they do.
Where are those keys, Amy?
- Amy, where are the keys?
- They're in the backpack.
No. We stay close.
We wait until we're found.
We keep someone always on guard.
We keep our wounds covered.
And we look out after each other.
That is the only way.
Somebody's coming.
One swallow apiece.
Stace.
It's still in there. I can feel it.
See, look how puffy it is.
That's just swelling. It's natural.
It's just what happens
when you cut yourself, okay?
He won't last much longer like this.
- We have to cut them off.
- Cut what off?
- His legs.
- Tell me you're joking.
- He'll die if we don't.
- Just please tell me you're joking.
He'll get infected, if he isn't already.
Septicemia.
Well, what the hell is septicemia, Jeff?
An infection, usually in the bones,
when it's exposed to bacteria.
You're fucking crazy.
No, I'm telling you,
he won't last through the day like this.
Without anesthesia?
He has no feeling beneath his waist.
The tourniquets are already in place.
We're gonna cut below them.
With what?
A knife?
We have to break the bones first
and then cut.
Well, we're not cutting his legs off
with a fucking hunting knife, Jeff.
There's no flesh
covering his bones, Eric.
He is going to die.
Okay. Okay, fine. Let's fucking vote.
You know, raise your hands
if you want to cut off his legs.
Stacy, what are you doing?
He's in med school, Eric.
Yeah. Yeah, he's in med school.
He's not a surgeon. He's not a doctor.
He's in school.
I'm entitled to my vote, Eric.
You do it.
Cut them off.
Yeah.
I'll break the bones first, with the stone,
then use the knife to cut through.
Okay.
We're heating the pan to cauterize
the wounds to stop the bleeding.
You're not gonna be able to feel a thing,
but if you want to bite down on this,
you can, just in case.
Eric, you ready?
You should wait in the tent.
Grab his feet.
That foot. Turn it up.
Hold him down! Eric! Eric!
God!
Jeff! Jeff! Jeff! Jeff!
It's okay.
- Eric!
- Jeff!
Hold him fucking still!
Jeff!
Jeff, he felt it, didn't he?
- He has nerve damage.
- Yeah.
He can't feel anything
beneath his waist.
He was screaming, Jeff.
He was screaming.
He was telling you to stop.
He was screaming. How could
he not feel it when he was screaming?
It's just the visual.
- It was him looking down and seeing it.
- This is so not okay!
We didn't have a choice, Amy.
Amy. It's...
Oh, my God. Holy shit.
Oh, God.
What the fuck.
Look, how can it do that?
Check your phone.
Let me see.
I just wanna go home.
Do you think Stacy's gonna be okay?
Yeah.
I mean, I got it out. I saw it come out.
Yeah, she just really believes...
You know how she is.
She gets something in her head and...
she convinces herself.
Do you think that
they're ever gonna find us?
Honestly?
I think making a run for it
is our only chance.
I know.
Amy, come here, come here.
Eric.
What the fuck?
What?
I heard you.
- You heard me what?
- I heard you fucking her.
Excuse me?
- Don't lie to me, Eric. I heard you.
- Stace.
I heard you. I heard you fucking her!
Stacy, come on.
How could you do that to me?
How could you guys fucking sit there
and fuck when I'm in the tent?
Stace, you need to calm down.
Don't tell me what I should do.
Stacy, you know I wouldn't do that.
- I heard you, Eric.
- We were just talking. I was just...
- I heard you moaning, Amy.
- I was crying, Stacy.
- What's going on?
- My boyfriend is fucking your girlfriend!
- That's what's going on.
- She's just crazy and irrational.
- You think she's never cheated on you?
- Stacy.
- Fuck you!
- Fuck you, bitch!
Fuck you! All you ever cared about
is your fucking self!
- Stacy, stop it.
- Don't fucking touch me!
Relax. You're scared.
She would've slept with Mathias
if I hadn't stopped her.
Mathias.
Well, thank God we cut his legs off.
Shut up.
It's eating me like it's eating him.
- Stace.
- No. It's inside. It's inside of me.
Stacy.
It's in my side, Amy. It's in my... It's...
I'll show you. It's here.
If you just cut here and here...
- Stacy.
...and here.
- Stacy, you're okay.
- You're okay.
- You're not listening!
- Stacy, you're fine.
You are not listening!
You're not listening to me!
What the fuck?
They don't want us to spread it.
That's why they won't let us leave.
They're salting the soil
to keep it contained.
It's old. It has to be. Really old.
Because the birds, the insects,
somehow they've learned
not to land here.
And the horses. Remember?
How frightened the horses were?
It didn't happen.
What she said about Mathias.
- I didn't...
- You don't have to say anything.
But I do.
- Because I don't want you to...
- Amy.
Look at us.
Would it matter to you?
Guys?
Show them.
- Okay. Stace.
- I didn't mean to.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- I know.
We're gonna start with the one
in your leg. Okay, Stace?
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- You might wanna close your eyes.
I wanna see. I wanna see it.
Stacey, keep breathing, okay?
Through your nose.
Good. Just keep breathing,
keep breathing.
Keep breathing.
Keep breathing. Keep breathing.
- Okay. Okay. All right, he's almost done.
- I got it.
It's okay.
Okay?
Should I stop?
Stacy, do you want me to stop?
No.
- I'm scared. No.
- It's okay. Keep breathing.
Okay, okay.
It's almost out.
No! Oh, no!
Oh, my God!
Okay, it's okay.
- He got all of it.
- The shirt up.
Hold the other one.
It's okay. I'm here.
Please.
Stace.
There's more of it. There's more.
Right here. Under. Under the muscle,
like by the bone there.
There's nothing there, Stacy.
- Yes, can we cut it?
- There's no more cutting.
I wanna cut it. I wanna cut it.
- I wanna cut it. I wanna...
- Hey, don't!
Hey! You can't. You can't keep cutting.
- It's just everywhere. It's in my head.
- No.
- It's okay. You're okay.
- No, no.
- Yeah, you're okay.
- No, no. I'm not okay. I'm not okay.
You keep saying I'm okay. I'm not okay.
Why do you keep saying that to me?
Here, this might help.
What? What?
Amy, did you see it?
You saw it, didn't you?
You saw it in my head. I felt it.
Amy.
Amy, please tell me.
- Stacy.
- Why won't you look at me?
Stacy, Stacy...
- You saw it?
- It's okay.
- You saw it? Did you see it?
- No, I... There's nothing there.
There's nothing there, okay? I swear.
It's in my head. I feel it, you guys.
- Let's move her in the tent.
- Okay.
No one's coming. I'm going tonight.
I wanna cut it.
I wanna cut it. I wanna cut it.
Stacy, what are you doing?
Oh, my God!
It's okay. It's okay.
I just... I just have to get this one out.
It's okay.
Just have to get this one.
- Stacy?
- No. No.
- Stacy, give it to me.
- Give it to me right now.
- No!
Jeff?
I'm very sorry.
- I have to get this piece right here...
- Stacy.
...in my...
- Stacy, give me the knife. Stacy.
Stacy, give me the knife, okay?
Don't touch me!
Easy, stay down.
Eric! Eric!
- Eric!
- Oh, my God!
Stay down.
Eric! Eric!
Eric! Amy!
Come here. Come here.
Amy! Eric! Eric!
Eric! Amy! Amy!
Amy, I didn't mean to! I'm sorry!
It hurts.
- It's okay.
- I didn't mean to!
- Stacy.
- Eric! Eric! It hurts.
Don't move. Don't move.
Eric?
Eric? Eric? Eric!
Eric? Eric?
No! No.
No! No!
- Eric! Eric!
- Come here. Come here.
Eric! Eric! Eric!
Stacy.
- Amy. Amy, it hurts.
- No.
- No. No.
- It hurts.
Kill me. Amy, kill me.
Amy.
Kill me. Kill me!
- Jeff.
- Amy!
- Kill me! Kill me!
- It's okay.
Stace.
You have to, Amy.
Kill me! Amy!
- Yes! Kill me! Kill me. Kill me!
- No!
- Kill me! Kill me! Kill me!
- Amy.
Jeff.
Kill me!
Kill me! Kill me! Kill me!
Once you're past the clearing,
you run as fast as you can, okay?
Okay?
When you get to the Jeep,
you don't wait for anything. Anything.
And if these don't work, then you run,
and you don't stop
until you reach the town.
You promise me that you'll still be here?
Okay.
You don't even know her name.
You don't know any of our names.
I'm Jeff. Jeff Dean Maclntyre.
Winnetka, Illinois.
Twenty-two years old.
I was gonna be a doctor.
That was my dream.
That's all I wanted.
You should know her name, too.
Her name
is Amy!
And she is not gonna die
on this fucking hill!
Jeff!
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Please.
Okay.
- Dimitri!
Dimitri!